### Tushar krishna

#### Full Stack Javascript Developer

A full stack javascript developer with a proven track record in designing websites, networking and managing databases with an experience of 3 years 3 months. I have strong technical skills as well as excellent interpersonal skills, enabling me to interact with a wide range of clients. I am eager to be challenged in order to grow and further improve my IT skills. My greatest passion in life is using my technical skills to benefit others and organisations.

tus	har.panuma	tcha@	)gmai	l.com	$\geq$

+91 8008168196

Hyderabad, India 👂

linkedin.com/in/tushar-krishna-panumatcha-9a5147194 in

quora.com/profile/Tushar-Krishna-12 Q

github.com/tusharpanumatcha 👩

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## **Full Stack Javascript Developer**Object Frontier Software

06/2019 - 03/2020

Project Name: FLMP

The client is an American corporation that produces flavors which it markets globally. The application will display all the data related to the current year sales and previous year sales with respect to the flavors sales. Providing a wide variety of filters to manipulate the

#### Roles/Responsibilities

- ROLE: Full Stack Javascript Developer, TEAM SIZE: 2.
- As a full stack developer, developed APIs using NodeJS and ExpressJS and integrated with angular components and reusable services.
- Worked as a single developer on the entire application.
- Customized inbuilt functionalities of syncfusion grid to meet client requirements.
- Created services to consume enterprise level third party services.
- Performed unit testing with more than 80% code coverage.
- Resolved production and deployment issues.

# **Full Stack Javascript Developer**Object Frontier Software

03/2019 - 07/2019

Project Name: FRMP

The Client is an American corporation that produces fragrances, and cosmetic actives, which it markets globally. The application will display all the data related to the current year sales and previous year sales with respect to the fragrancessales. Providing a wide variety of filters to manipulate the data and exporting the data in different formats.

#### Roles/Responsibilities

- ROLE: Full Stack Javascript Developer, TEAM SIZE: 4
- Developed front-end using HTML5 and designed UI components using angular 6. Implemented integrated multiple modules.
- Developed code with proper standards using MVC architecture.
- Supported to release by solving production issues and involved in code deployment.
- Integrated with Node API's and interfacing 3rd party
- Performed unit testing with more than 80% code coverage
- Resolved production and deployment issues

#### **SOFT SKILLS**

Decision Making

Versatility

Team playe

Good Communication

Self-motivation

#### **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

#### **Programming Languages**

C, Java, Python, Javascript, Typescript

#### Front end Frameworks/Libraries

Angular, React.js, JQuery, HTML, CSS and AJAX

#### Server side Frameworks/Run-time

Node.js, Nest.js, Express.js, Hapi.js and Koa.js

#### **Database Technologies**

MySQL, PostgreSQL and MongoDB

#### ORM/ODM

Sequelize and Mongoose

#### **Tools and Utilities**

Webpack

#### **Version Control**

git

#### **Cloud Technologies**

Azure - IAAS (VM, VNet, Load Balancer), PAAS (Web Apps, Function Apps) and SAAS (SQL server, Cosmos DB, Cognitive services)

#### Domain Knowledge

Insurance, Medical Coding and Manufacturing

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### Full Stack Javascript Developer Object Frontier Software

02/2018 - 02/2019

Project Name: GYM Coding

The Client is a healthcare information management company with headquarters in Alpharetta, Georgia. The application provides medical coding training for beginner. It provides pdf related functionalities like annotations, fit to size, rotation and zooming.

#### Roles/Responsibilities

- ROLE: Full Stack Javascript Developer, TEAM SIZE: 4.
- Worked on developing pdf annotation feature from scratch using fabric.js and pdf.js.
- Implemented features like lazy loading, role based access and state management
- Worked on reusable services.

# **Full Stack Javascript Developer**Object Frontier Software

08/2017 - 02/2018

Project Name: Health-Source

The Client is a healthcare information management company with headquarters in Alpharetta, Georgia. The application provides medical records of the patient in the form of pdf.

#### Roles/Responsibilities

- ROLE: Full Stack Javascript Developer, TEAM SIZE: 3
- Worked on functionalities like scanning and rendering the medical records in the form of pdf
- Worked on plagiarism checking algorithm and natural language processing to differentiate the medical records.

#### **CERTIFICATES**

C Programming certification (07/2013 - Present)

Microsoft Azure Certified Developer – Associate

Node.js certification

#### **EDUCATION**

#### **Bachelor of Engineering**

B V Raju Institute of Technology(JNTU)

06/2013 - 04/2017

68.8%

Stream

 B.Tech, Electronics and Communication Engineering.

#### Intermediate Board

Narayana junior College, Hyderabad, Telangana

06/2011 - 03/2013

93%

Stream:

 M.P.C (Mathematics, Physics, Chemistry)

### Tenth State Board

Narayana Concept School

06/2010 - 03/2011 90.6%

#### **ACHIEVEMENTS**

NCC Cadet (06/2011 - 06/2013)

National Cadet Corps

 The National Cadet Corps is the youth wing of Armed Forces with its headquarters at New Delhi, Delhi, India. It is open to school and college students on voluntary basis.

### Elected as department representative (07/2015 - 07/2016)

B.V. Raju Institute of technology

 During this academic period, I have organised a National level symposium and conducted many events like Quiz, Paper Presentation, Project Presentation etc.

#### Secured Second prize in college level debate (06/2014)

B.V. Raju Institute of technology

 During this academic period, I have participated in college level debate competition, in which I secured third prize

#### **LANGUAGES**

English	
Hindi	$\bullet$ $\bullet$ $\circ$ $\circ$
Telugu	$\bullet$ $\bullet$ $\bullet$ $\circ$
Tamil	

#### **INTERESTS**

Web Development | Mobile applications

Badminton

Cricket

**Cloud Computing** 

Movies